Guide to the School of Law Records, 1914-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- Deans Papers, 1929-1999, undated, 95 Linear Feet (63.5 boxes)
  - Dean A. Kenneth Pye, 1970-1977, undated.
    - Calendar, Proposed for 1974-1976, 1973, 1975 (Box 39)
    - Civil Rights, undated (Box 39)
    - Clinical Education, 1973-1976 (Box 39)
    - Clinical Program for Older Americans, 1975-1976, undated (Box 39)
    - Commencements, 1973-1976 (Box 39)
    - Committees, Admissions, 1974-1976 (Box 39)
    - Committees, Commencement, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
    - Committees, Curriculum, 1973-1976 (2 folders) (Box 39)
    - Committees, Faculty Appointments, 1973-1977, undated (Box 39)
    - Committees, First Year Legal Research and Writing, 1973-1975, undated (1 of 3 folders) (Box 39)
    - Committees, First Year Legal Research and Writing, 1973-1975, undated (folders 2 and 3 of 3) (Box 40)
    - Committees, General, 1973-1976, undated (Box 40)
    - Committees, Grants and Special Projects, 1973-1976, undated (Box 40)
    - Committees, Law School Publications, 1973-1974, undated (Box 40)
    - Committees, Library, 1973-1975 (Box 40)
    - Committees, Long Range Planning, 1973-1976, undated (Box 40)
    - Committees, Placement, 1973-1975, undated (Box 40)
    - Committees, Research and Writing, 1975 (Box 40)
    - Committees, Special Occasions and Alumni Relations, 1973-1975 (Box 40)
    - Committees, Student Faculty, 1973-1974, undated (Box 40)
    - Confidential Profile, 1970-1973, undated (Box 40)
    - Constitutional Remedies (Lee's Campaign), 1975-1976, undated (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Contests, 1973-1975, undated (Box 40)
    - Correspondence, Chancellor, 1973-1976 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence, Counsel, 1974-1976 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence, General, 1973-1976 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence, President, 1973-1976 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence, Provost, 1974-1976 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence, Students, 1973-1976 (Box 40)
    - Council on Foundations, Inc., 1971, 1973 (Box 40)
    - Council on Legal Education for Professional Responsibility, 1973-1976 (Box 40)
    - Court Cases, Department of Justice, 1976-1977 (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Court Re-Organization, 1973 (Box 40)
    - Criminal Justice, 1975 (Box 40)
    - Criminal Justice, Institute of Government, 1973-1975, undated (Box 40)
    - Criminal Justice Legislative Bulletin, 1974-1975 (Box 40)
    - Criminal Procedures, 1971, 1975-1977 (Box 40)
    - Curriculum, Course and Seminar Questionaires, 1973 (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Curriculum, Scheduling, 1974-1976 (Box 40)
    - Currie, Brainerd, 1973-1976 (Box 40)
    - Danforth Project, 1975, undated (Box 40)
    - Dean Searches, 1973-1975 (Box 40)
    - Development, 1974-1976, undated (Box 40)
    - Devil's Advocate, 1974, undated (Box 41)
    - Duke Bar Association, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Duke Endowment, 1973-1976, undated (Box 41)
    - Duke University General, 1972-1974 (Box 41)
    - Earl Warren Legal Training Program, 1973-1975 (Box 41)
    - Elderly Program, 1973-1974 (Box 41)
    - Enrollment Statistics, 1973-1976 (Box 41)
    - Environmental Law, 1973-1974 (Box 41)
    - Epoch Campaign, 1975-1977 (Box 41)
    - Faculty Club, 1972-1974, undated (Box 41)
    - Faculty Correspondence with Walter Dellinger, meetings, 1973-1977 (Box 41)
    - Faculty Lists, 1973-1976, undated (Box 41)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 41)
    - Faculty Prospects, 1973-1976 (Box 41)
    - Faculty Prospects, Institute of Policy Sciences, 1972-1974, undated (Box 41)
    - Faculty Prospects, Letters of Recommendation, 1973-1975 (Box 41)
    - Faculty Prospects, Meetings, 1973-1977, undated (Box 41)
    - Faculty Prospects, Rejects, 1974-1975, undated (Box 41)
    - Faculty Prospects, Resumes, 1973-1975, undated (Box 41)
    - Faculty Prospects, Searches from Others, 1973-1975 (Box 41)
    - Faculty Prospects, Visitors, 1973-1977 (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Faculty Sabbatical Requests, 1974-1975 (Box 41)
    - Faculty Tenured, 1973-1977 (Box 41)
    - Faculty Union, 1973, undated (Box 41)
    - Federal Rules of Evidence News, 1976 (Box 41)
    - Financial Aid, 1973-1976 (Box 41)
    - Forum on War, Brown, 1974, undated (Box 41)
    - Funded Legal Education Program Students, 1975 (Box 41)
    - Fundraising, 1971-1972, 1975, undated (Box 41)
    - Gift Prospects, 1973-1975 (Box 41)
    - Gift Statistics, 1970, 1975-1976, undated (Box 41)
    - Governor's Advisory Committee for Human Rights, 1973 (Box 41)
    - Grading, 1973-1976 (Box 41)
    - Grad Faculty, 1974-1976 (Box 41)
    - Heating and Air Conditioning, 1973-1976 (Box 41)
    - Impact Study Briefs and Cases, 1973-1975, undated (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Impact Study Cases, 1973-1975, undated (Box 41)
    - Indiana Bar, 1973-1976 (Box 41)
    - Institute for Trial Advocacy, 1974-1976 (Box 42)
    - Insurance, 1976 (Box 42)
    - International Studies, 1974-1976 (Box 42)
    - J.D. - M.B.A., 1973-1975, undated (Box 42)
    - J.D. - M.H.A. Program, 1973-1976, undated (Box 42)
    - Jafree Case, 1972-1974 (Box 42)
    - Job Descriptions, 1973-1974, undated (Box 42)
    - Joint Degree, Miscellaneous, 1974-1975, undated (Box 42)
    - Joint Programs, L.L.M. Degree, 1945-1946, 1973-1976, undated (Box 42)
    - Joint Degree, 3/3 Program, 1974-1976 (Box 42)
    - Joint Degree, J.D. - M.D., 1973, undated (Box 42)
    - Judicial Board Code, 1973-1976, undated (Box 42)
    - Justice Department, 1976 (Box 42)
    - Law Alumni, 1975 (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1973-1976, undated (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems Editorship, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Law Dames, 1973-1974 (Box 42)
    - Law Day, 1974-1976, undated (Box 42)
    - Law Forum (Speakers), 1974-1976 (Box 42)
    - Law Journal, 1973-1976 (Box 42)
    - Law Library, 1973-1976, undated (Box 42)
    - Law School Admissions Council, 1974-1976 (Box 42)
    - Law Schools, Materials Relating to, 1974-1976, undated (Box 42)
    - Law Student Council Minority Admissions, 1974-1975, undated (Box 42)
    - Legal Aid, 1972-1974, undated (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - Legal Questions, Related to Defender Project, 1973-1975 (Box 42)
    - Legal Research, 1973-1976 (Box 42)
    - Legal Services, 1973-1975, undated (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - Librarian Prospects, 1974, undated (Box 42)
    - Life Income Fund, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Loyalty Fund, Donors Letters, 1973-1977 (Box 42)
    - Loyalty Fund, General, 1973-1976 (Box 42)
    - Loyalty Fund Statistics, 1973-1977 (Box 42)
    - Maintenance, 1973-1976 (Box 42)
    - Medical Center, 1973-1975 (Box 42)
    - Mini Courses, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1976 (Box 43)
    - Mock Trials, 1975-1977, undated (Box 43)
    - Moot Court, 1975-1976 (Box 43)
    - Moot Court, Dean's Cup, 1973-1974 (Box 43)
    - Mordecai Society, 1974-1976 (Box 43)
    - National Council of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1976 (Box 43)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities Grants, 1974-1977 (Box 43)
    - New Jersey, 1976-1977, undated (Box 43)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, Committee on Continuing Education, 1973-1975 (Box 43)
    - North Carolina Bar Exam, 1976 (Box 43)
    - North Carolina Bar Examiners, 1973 (Box 43)
    - North Carolina Bar Foundation, 1973-1976 (Box 43)
    - North Carolina Council on State Goals and Policy, 1973, undated (Box 43)
    - North Carolina Law Examiners, 1974-1975 (Box 43)
    - North Carolina Public Interest Research Group, Police Protection, 1974, undated (Box 43)
    - Order of the Coif, 1972-1976 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 43)
    - Order of the Coif, 1972-1976 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 43)
    - Organizations, 1974-1976 (Box 43)
    - Paralegal, 1973-1974 (Box 43)
    - Phi Alpha Delta, 1973-1975, undated (Box 43)
    - Placement, 1973-1976 (4 folders) (Box 43)
    - Pre-Law, 1974-1976 (Box 43)
    - Publications, 1967, 1970, 1974-1976, undated (Box 43)
    - Quail Roost Faculty Conference, 1972-1975 (Box 43)
    - Questions, Law School, 1973-1976 (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Recruiting Plans, 1973-1975 (Box 44)
    - Recruiting, 1974-1976, (folders 1 and 2 of 3) (Box 44)
    - Recruiting, 1974-1976, (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 44)
    - Report to Alumni, 1976 (Box 44)
    - Round Table on Science and Public Affairs, 1975-1976 (Box 44)
    - Sabbaticals, 1974-1975 (Box 44)
    - Scheduling, 1973-1976 (Box 44)
    - Self Study, 1975-1976 (Box 44)
    - Society for Religion in Higher Education, 1974-1975 (Box 44)
    - Southern Regional Growth Board, 1971-1973 (Box 44)
    - Student Directories, 1976-1977, undated (Box 44)
    - Teacher Evaluations, 1963, 1975-1976, undated (Box 44)
    - Teachers Insurance Annuity Assocation, 1973, undated (Box 44)
    - Third Year Practice, 1973-1976 (Box 44)
    - Tuition, 1974-1976 (Box 44)
    - Triangle Universities Computation Center, 1973, undated (Box 44)
    - University Cousel, General Correspondence, personal, 1971-1972 (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Withdrawls, 1974-1975 (Box 44)
    - Xerox, 1974-1976, undated (Box 44)
  - Dean Walter E. Dellinger III (Acting Dean), 1974-1978, undated.
    Walter E. Dellinger served as acting dean between 1976-1978. Prior to becoming acting dean, Dellinger was the associate dean of the law school. Some documents in this subseries are likely from his time as associate dean. There is also some overlap between the papers of Dean Dellinger and Dean Carrington.
    - Academic Council, 1977-1978 (Box 44)
    - Addresses, Faculty, Boards and Other, 1976-1978 (Box 44)
    - Admissions, 1977-1978 (Box 44)
    - Alumni Newsletter, Weekend, Affiars and Other, 1976-1978 (Box 44)
    - American Bar Association, 1977-1978 (Box 44)
    - American Bar Association Questionaire, 1976-1977, undated (Box 44)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1975-1977 (Box 44)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1977-1978 (Box 44)
    - Association of American Law Schools Hearing Examiners, 1976 (Box 44)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Southeastern Conference, 1975-1976 (Box 44)
    - Bar, 1978 (Box 44)
    - Barristers, 1977 (Box 44)
    - Board of Visitors Meeting, 1977 (Box 44)
    - Class Schedules, 1977-1978 (Box 44)
    - Commencements, 1970, 1972, 1977-1978, undated (Box 44)
    - Committees, 1977-1978 (Box 44)
    - Committees, Curriculum, 1977, undated (Box 44)
    - Committees, Faculty Appointments, 1977 (Box 44)
    - Committee Grants, undated (Box 44)
    - Committee, Long Range Planning, 1977 (Box 44)
    - Competitions and Contests, 1977, undated (Box 44)
    - Correspondence, Chancellor, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, General, 1977 (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, General, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, President, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, Provost, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, Students, 1977 (Box 45)
    - Currie, Brainerd, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - Dean Searches, 1977 (Box 45)
    - Dean Searches, Other Schools, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - Duke Bar Association, 1977 (Box 45)
    - Faculty and Staff Address List, 1977 (Box 45)
    - Faculty Correspondence, 1977-1978 (2 folders) (Box 45)
    - Faculty, General, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - Faculty Meetings and Memoranda, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - Faculty Prospects, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - Faculty Prospects, Letters of Recommendation, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Foreign Students, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Fundraising, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - Gifts and Contributions, 1976-1977 (Box 45)
    - Grading, 1977 (Box 45)
    - Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, 1973-1977 (Box 45)
    - Judicial Board Code, 1978, undated (Box 45)
    - Justice Department, 1977 (2 folders) (Box 45)
    - Law Forum (Speakers), 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - Law Journal, 1977 (Box 45)
    - Law School Calendar, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - Law School Publications, undated (Box 45)
    - Librarians Assembly, 1978 (Box 45)
    - M.A. in Law, undated (Box 45)
    - Marshall (Patricia) Versus Duke University, 1976 (Box 45)
    - Meeting, Executive Council, April 5, 1974 (Box 45)
    - Minority Admissions, 1977, undated (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976, undated (Box 45)
    - Moot Court, 1974-1978 (Box 45)
    - Moot Court, 1977 (Box 45)
    - Moot Court Finals, 1976 (Box 45)
    - Murphy, Chas S. Award, 1976 (Box 45)
    - Nathan Burkan Competition, 1975 (Box 45)
    - "Next to the Bottom Line" Conference, 1977 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Academy of Trial Lawyers, 1977 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, 1978 (Box 45)
    - North Carolina Law Examiners, 1977 (Box 45)
    - Order of the Coif, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Paulsen, Monrad (Dean), 1974 (Box 45)
    - Placement, 1975 (Box 45)
    - Placement, 1976 (Box 45)
    - Placement, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - Policy, 1974, undated (Box 45)
    - Policy News, 1976 (Box 45)
    - Pollitt, Daniel, 1975 (Box 45)
    - Pre-Law, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Presidential Power Symposium, 1975 (Box 45)
    - Pye, Kenneth A., 1975-1976 (Box 45)
    - Pye, Kennethy A. Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 45)
    - Questions, Law School, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - Rating, Duke, 1976 (Box 45)
    - Recommendations, Facutly, 1974 (Box 45)
    - Recommendations, Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 45)
    - Recommendations, Letters, 1976 (Box 45)
    - Recommendations, Students, 1974-1975 (Box 45)
    - Recruiter Packet, 1975 (Box 45)
    - Recruitment File, 1974-1975 (Box 45)
    - Report to the Consultatnt on Legal Education to the American Bar Association, 1976-1977 (Box 45)
    - Reynolds Proposal, undated (Box 45)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1975 (Box 45)
    - Schedule, 1974-1976 (Box 45)
    - Schedule, 1976-1977 (Box 45)
    - School of Law Report to the Academic Affairs Committee of the Board of Trustees, December 12, 1975 (Box 45)
    - Smith, James, 1974 (Box 45)
    - Speech to Entering Class, 1977 (Box 45)
    - Southeast Regional Association of American Law Schools, 1976 (Box 45)
    - Statistics for the 1975 Entering Class, 1975 (Box 45)
    - Student Assignments, 1976, undated (Box 45)
    - Student Directories, undated (Box 45)
    - Students, Individual Correspondence, 1976 (Box 45)
    - Students on or Removed from Probation, 1974 (Box 45)
    - Tuition, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
    - University Judical Board, 1978 (Box 45)
    - University Policy, Alcoholic Beverages, undated (Box 45)
    - University Salaries, undated (Box 45)
    - University Self-Study, 1975 (Box 45)
  - Dean Paul Carrington, 1968-1989, bulk 1978-1988, undated.
    Paul Carrington was dean of the law school from 1978 to 1988. This material is restricted for 25 years from date of origin. Contact research services for more information. Also, there is some overlap between Dean Carrington and Dean Dellinger's papers so other Carrington related material may be found in the Dellinger subseries.
    - Accreditation, 1979-1980 (Box 46)
    - American Bar Association, 1977 (Box 46)
    - American Bar Association, 1978 (Box 46)
    - American Bar Association, Chicago Meeting, 1979 (Box 46)
    - American Bar Association, Indo-Chinese Refugee Legal Assistance Program, 1980 (Box 46)
    - American Bar Association Inspection, 1979 (Box 46)
    - American Bar Association Journal, 1980 (Box 46)
    - American Bar Association, Judicial Reform Committee, 1978, undated (Box 46)
    - American Bar Association Meeting, 1978, undated (Box 46)
    - American Bar Association Study Group, 1979, undated (Box 46)
    - American Bar Association Questionaire, Faculty Information and Other, 1976, 1978-1979, undated (2 folders) (Box 46)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1979 (Box 46)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Federal Financing of Legal Education, 1978-1980, (2 folders) (Box 46)
    - Bar Exam Results, 1981 (Box 46)
    - Chief Justiceship, 1979 (Box 46)
    - Duke Law Forum, 1979 (Box 46)
    - Duke University, Canadian Studies, 1978-1980 (Box 46)
    - Duke University, Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 46)
    - Department of Economics, Oeconophile, 1977-1978 (Box 46)
    - Entering Class Statistics, 1980 (Box 46)
    - East Campus Committee, 1979-1981 (2 folders) (Box 46)
    - East Campus Plans, undated (Box 46)
    - Fuquay, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Inspection Reports, 1976 (Box 46)
    - International Court of Justice, 1981 (Box 46)
    - Judge Oxner, Canadian Visitor, 1979 (Box 46)
    - Law Journal, 1978, undated (Box 46)
    - Mandamus, 1981 (Box 46)
    - National Humanities Center, 1977-1979 (Box 46)
    - North Carolina Bar, 1980 (Box 46)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, 1976-1979 (Box 46)
    - North Carolina Bar Assocation 1978 Exam, 1978-1979 (Box 46)
    - Numerical Key to Law Schools in the United States, 1976-1977 (Box 46)
    - Policy, 1968, 1977, undated (Box 46)
    - Second Circuit Judicial Conference, 1981 (Box 46)
    - South American Trip 1980, 1979-1981 (Box 46)
    - United States Courts, Standards for Admission, Devitt Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 46)
    - Admissions Statistics comparative Study for 1963-1981 Entering Class, 1981 (Box 47)
    - Admission Statistics for 1976 Entering Class, 1976 (Box 47)
    - Admission Statistics for 1978 Entering Class, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Admission Statistics for 1981 Entering Class, 1981 (Box 47)
    - Admission Statistics for 1981-1985 Entering Classes, 1981-1985 (Box 47)
    - Advisory Council, 1982 (Box 47)
    - Alumni Affairs, Stanford and Chicago, 1980 (Box 47)
    - Alumni Meetings, Schedules, 1978-1981 (Box 47)
    - Alumni Publication, 1981 (Box 47)
    - American Bar Association, national Institute of Justice, 1981 (Box 47)
    - Annual Giving, 1983 (Box 47)
    - Annual Report for the Law School, 1983-1987 (Box 47)
    - Appointments and Promotions, 1979 (Box 47)
    - Canadian Federalism II (Leach and Pye), 1982 (Box 47)
    - Center for International Studies, 1981-1982 (Box 47)
    - Clinical Program, 1980-1982 (Box 47)
    - Clinical Program Grant Application, 1980 (Box 47)
    - Clinical Studies Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 47)
    - Course Schedules, 1980-1981 (Box 47)
    - Curriculum, 1977-1978 (Box 47)
    - Curriculum, 1978-1979 (Box 47)
    - Curriculum, 1979-1980 (Box 47)
    - Curriculum, 1979-1981 (Box 47)
    - Curriculum, 1981-1982 (Box 47)
    - Duke University, Alumni Affairs, 1978-1985 (Box 47)
    - Duke University, Financial Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 47)
    - Duke University Library, 1980-1981 (Box 47)
    - Duke University Planning Committee, 1978, 1980 (Box 47)
    - Duke University Sabbatical Leave, 1977 (Box 47)
    - Durham Chamber of Commerce, 1977-1984 (Box 47)
    - Faculty Newsletter, A Report from the Law School, 1981 (Box 47)
    - Judicial Center, 1977 (Box 47)
    - Honor Code, 1971, 1977, undated (Box 47)
    - Immigration (Hofstetter), 1981-1983 (Box 47)
    - Journal of International and Comparative Law, 1980 (Box 47)
    - Judges and Prosecutors, 1980-1981 (Box 47)
    - Judicial Administration, Selected problems In, 1982 (Box 47)
    - Law Library Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 47)
    - Law Library Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 47)
    - Law Library Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 47)
    - Law Library Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 47)
    - Law Library Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 47)
    - Law Library Personnel, 1980, undated (Box 47)
    - Law School Judicial Board, 1971, 1978-1981 (Box 47)
    - Law School Surveys, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Legal Research, 1980-1981 (Box 47)
    - Legal Services, 1981 (Box 47)
    - Michael S. Scofield Criminal Law Award, 1979, undated (Box 47)
    - Minority Recruiting, 1977 (Box 47)
    - Law School Long Range Planning and Self-Evaluation, 1974, 1978-1979 (Box 48)
    - First year Calendar, Small Section Program, 1980 (Box 48)
    - North Carolina Academy of Trial Lawyers, 1978 (Box 48)
    - North Carolina Center for Public Policy Research Inc, 1979 (Box 48)
    - North Carolina Prisoner Legal Services, 1977-1978 (Box 48)
    - Soviet Law, 1978 (Box 48)
    - Law Library, 1978-1988 (4 folders) (Box 48)
    - Levin, Betsy, Grant, 1977-1981 (Box 48)
    - Dellinger, Walter, 1981 (Box 48)
    - Schmalbeck, R., 1981-1982 (Box 48)
    - Havighurst, Clark, 1981-1982 (Box 48)
    - Zell, Jonathan, 1979-1983 (Box 48)
    - Lewis, James, 1979 (Box 48)
    - Malkinson, Carol, 1983 (Box 48)
    - Munsinger, Harry, Independent Study, 1984 (Box 48)
    - Sapp, Judith, 1984 (Box 48)
    - Scioscia, David, 1983-1984 (Box 48)
    - Banov, Mark, 1980 (Box 48)
    - Cohen, Ruth, 1982 (Box 48)
    - Crane, Peter, 1983 (Box 48)
    - Empson, Nick, 1979-1983 (Box 48)
    - Friedman, Laurence, 1983-1984 (Box 48)
    - Lawlor, Patrick, 1980 (Box 48)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Faculty Grievance, 1985 (Box 48)
    - Administrative Committee, 1979-1987 (Box 48)
    - Committee Assignments, 1978-1987 (Box 48)
    - Correspondence, Student, 1978-1983 (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - Moore, Alfred D., 1982 (Box 48)
    - Nut File, 1974-1984 (Box 48)
    - Havighurst Purchases, 1981 (Box 48)
    - Library Renovation, 1979-1983 (Box 48)
    - Library Committee, 1980-1984 (Box 48)
    - CAP Gifts, 1986-1987 (Box 48)
    - Duke Bar Association Correspondence, 1977-1986 (Box 49)
    - Duke Bar Association, General, 1977-1986 (Box 49)
    - Dean's Council Minutes, 1980-1986 (3 folders) (Box 49)
    - Applications for Teaching Positions, 1984-1985 (3 folders) (Box 49)
    - Curriculum, 1982-1983 (Box 49)
    - Curriculum, 1983-1984 (Box 49)
    - Curriculum, 1983-1985 (Box 49)
    - Curriculum, 1986-1987 (Box 49)
    - Curriculum, 1987-1988 (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1985 (Box 49)
    - Continuing Legal Education Broadcasts, undated (Box 49)
    - Duke Pacific Law Society, 1985 (Box 49)
    - Beale, Sara Sun, 1983-1984, undated (4 folders) (Box 49)
    - Schmalbeck, Richard, 1981-1984, undated (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - National Humanities Center, Duke Law School, 1978-1981 (Box 50)
    - North Carolina National Bank, Student Loan, 1972-1976 (Box 50)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, Committee on Continuing Legal Education, 1980-1982 (Box 50)
    - Pacific Duke Law Club, 1980 (Box 50)
    - President's Report to Trustees, 1983-1985 (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - Publications Board Report, 1971 (Box 50)
    - Recruiting, 1976-1977 (Box 50)
    - Recruitment of Women Faculty, 1977 (Box 50)
    - Research Office, 1986 (Box 50)
    - Schedules and Assignments, 1978-1979 (Box 50)
    - Scholarships, Haywood Robbins, 1969-1971 (Box 50)
    - Scholarships, Hedrick Scholarship Fund, 1967-1969 (Box 50)
    - Securities Industry Association, 1979-1980 (Box 50)
    - Self Study Report, 1965, 1975-1976 (Box 50)
    - Seminar on Law and the Humanities, 1978-1979 (Box 50)
    - Senior Fellows, 1979-1980 (Box 50)
    - Senior Fellows, 1980-1981 (Box 50)
    - Senior Fellows, 1981-1982 (Box 50)
    - Stanford and Chicago Alumni Affairs and Development, 1980 (Box 50)
    - Admissions, 1977-1978 (Box 50)
    - Admissions, 1978-1979 (Box 50)
    - Admissions, 1979-1980 (Box 50)
    - Faculty Publications General, 1969-1983 (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - Admissions Policy, 1979 (Box 50)
    - Admissions Recruiting, 1978-1980 (Box 50)
    - Scholarship Listings, 1979, undated (Box 50)
    - Student Law Collections, 1979 (Box 50)
    - Affirmative Action, 1973-1980 (3 folders) (Box 50)
    - Admissions Committee Report, 1974 (Box 50)
    - Scholarships, 1978 (Box 50)
    - North Carolina Board of Law Examiners, 1978 (Box 50)
    - Law Alumni Association Council Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 50)
    - Law Alumni Weekend, 1978 (Box 50)
    - Alumni and Special Occasions, undated (Box 50)
    - Law Alumni and Academic Careers, undated (Box 50)
    - Alumni, 1975-1980 (Box 50)
    - Environmental Law Developments, 1977 (Box 50)
    - Law Library Annual Report, 1977 (Box 50)
    - Earl Warren Legal Training Program, 1979-1981 (Box 50)
    - Curriculum, 1977 (Box 50)
    - Judicial Code Revision Committee, 1981 (Box 50)
    - First Year Calendar, 1981 (Box 50)